https://www.aldoussystems.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Menu
Access ControlBase IP IntercomForce IP IntercomSolo IP IntercomUni IP IntercomVerso IP IntercomSafetyOEM KitAnswering UnitsAccess Control UnitsAccess CommanderSoftwareELAN Video DoorbellAccessoriesAudio SystemsMulti Room AudioCasaTunesELAN IP AudioAmplifiersControlMatricesStreamersInput PlatesInfra RedSpeaker SwitchersVolume ControlsAccessoriesCablesBulk CableTOSlinkAV LeadsPatch LeadsHDMI CablesFibreAccessoriesControl SystemsControllersTouchscreensKeypadsRemote ControlsInfra RedTemplatesAccessoriesSoftwareData NetworkingADSL/VDSL ModemRoutersWireless APsEthernet SwitchesAccessoriesEthernet Over CoaxEthernet Over Twister PairEthernet Over 2 WireHD Audio/Video DistributionMatrix SwitchersSplittersSwitchersConverters & ScalersExtendersVideo Over IPPackagesModulatorStreamingReceiverTransmitterVideo WallAccessoriesHeating ControlIP TelephonyVirtual PBX3CXAVLinkProVideo ConferencingLighting ControlDimmersRelaysLight SwitchesAccessoriesPowerPower ConditioningUPSVoltage RegulatorsPower CablesPower SuppliesAccessoriesIP PDUPublic AddressSecurityPanelsKeypadsWireless SensorsWired SensorsSoundersTouchscreensSoftwareAccessoriesSpeakersIn CeilingIn WallSubwooferOutdoorCabinet & On WallSoundbarEnclosuresGrillsCover PlatesBracketsFire HoodsAccessoriesStructured Cabling19" Racks19" Patch Panels19" ShelvesSOHO EnclosuresSOHO Patch PanelsTV DistributionConnectors & AdaptersFaceplates & ModulesWall MountVersaBoxAccessoriesSurveillanceIP CamerasDomeBulletTurretPTZFisheyeAnalogue CamerasDomeBulletTurretPTZNVRsDVRsCamera MountsControlBundlesAudioVirtual TechnicianSystem MonitoringToolsClearanceTraining CoursesThe Aldous Academy - Online Training2N TrainingAraknis TrainingELAN TrainingRako Training
Brands
All Brands
A
B
C
D
E
F
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Aldous Systems (Europe) Ltd uses and protects any information that you give Aldous Systems (Europe) Ltd when you use this website. Aldous Systems (Europe) Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Aldous Systems (Europe) Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and company name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as address and phone number so we can do business with you
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to to do business with you and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping so that we can do business with you.
We do NOT sell your data to 3rd parties
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you in relation to an order or to update you on new products. This will normally be via email or phone.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information abou our products and services which we think you may find interesting.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 and GDPR regulations brought into effect in May 2018. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to
or email us and this will be actioned within 30 days of receipt of the request.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
You have the right to request your data be deleted. If you require this, please write or email us and will action this within 30 days of receipt of the request.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
© 2017 Aldous Systems (Europe) Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
